<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>All Posts - Guodong's Blog</title><link>https://natelol.github.io/posts/</link><description>All Posts | Guodong's Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 19:40:37 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://natelol.github.io/posts/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>QQ to Apple Music Playlist</title><link>https://natelol.github.io/qq-to-apple-music-playlist/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 19:40:37 +0800</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://natelol.github.io/qq-to-apple-music-playlist/</guid><description><![CDATA[<div class="featured-image">
                <img src="/playlist.png" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
            </div>I came to find out that I can no longer listen to QQ music since I moved here to Singapore. That is definitely something I need to take care of since we all need some of the medoly to boost our work. After a quick seach, I have found this perticular approach that can help with that. What&rsquo;s more, new Apple music subscriber would have a long period of 3 months free service.]]></description></item><item><title>Opening of the blog!</title><link>https://natelol.github.io/10-10-2020/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2020 19:54:20 +0800</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://natelol.github.io/10-10-2020/</guid><description><![CDATA[<div class="featured-image">
                <img src="/10-10-2020.png" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
            </div>After few hours of template searching, I have found myself this particular template that I love. So, it&rsquo;s official now! I have a new blog running.
As the first post here, I would like to record the process of creating and deploying this blog so people who wants to do the same can have some reference. Hope this post can be helpful!
Prerequisites This blog is built with Hugo and one of the popular themes LoveIt.]]></description></item><item><title/><link>https://natelol.github.io/neighbour-component-analysis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://natelol.github.io/neighbour-component-analysis/</guid><description><![CDATA[neighbou&mdash; title: &ldquo;Neighbour Components Anaysis&rdquo; date: 2020-10-11T20:40:22+08:00 draft: false author: &ldquo;Guodong&rdquo; authorLink: &quot;&quot; description: &ldquo;NCA&rdquo; license: &quot;&quot; images: []
tags: [nca] categories: [ML] featuredImage: &ldquo;NCA.png&rdquo;
hiddenFromHomePage: false hiddenFromSearch: false twemoji: false lightgallery: true ruby: true fraction: true fontawesome: true linkToMarkdown: true rssFullText: false
toc: enable: true auto: true code: copy: true math: enable: true mapbox: accessToken: &quot;&quot; share: enable: true comment: enable: false Neighbour Components Analysis (NCA) learns a linear transfromation for the input space such that in the transformed space, KNN performs well.]]></description></item></channel></rss>